Guide to the KUHT Records 1997-006
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
KUHT Records
1950-2000
1960-1990
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
KUHT-TV (Television station: Houston, Tex.)
1997-006
234.00 Linear Feet
The KUHT Records includes correspondence, memoranda, publications, clippings, photographs, and related material dating from the 1950s through the 1990s. The bulk of the material dates from the mid-1960s to 1990s.
Historical Note:
KUHT-TV debuted on May 25, 1953, as America's first educational television station. Since then it has served as a model for other educational television stations. Its main goal is to provide quality programming to students, faculty, and the entire community. KUHT predates the Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) and the Public Broadcasting System (PBS). Its history includes award-winning local and national productions, including a national Emmy Award for excellence. KUHT is licensed to the University of Houston, and is located in the LeRoy and Lucile Melcher Center for Public Broadcasting located at 4343 Elgin, on the northeast corner of the main campus.
Accruals:
Additional 236 unprocessed boxes acquired July 11, 2014.
Additional unprocessed boxes arrived in September 2015.
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Related Archival Material:
KUHT Film and Video
Digital Collections:
KUHT Highlights digital collection (http://digital.lib.uh.edu/collection/p15195coll38)
KUHT items in the UH Audio/Video Repository (https://av.lib.uh.edu/?f%5Bcollection_ssim%5D%5B%5D=KUHT+Film+and+Video)
Scope and Contents
The KUHT Records includes correspondence, memoranda, publications, clippings, photographs, and related material dating from the 1950s through the 1990s. The bulk of the material dates from the mid-1960s to 1990s.
Please contact the collection curator Emily Vinson (evinson@uh.edu) for further information.
The series in the collection include: Discrepancy Files, Development and Production Files by Jim Fisher and Paul Yeager, Gulf Region Education Television Affiliates (GRETA), Photographs, Ephemera, Awards, Publications, and Scrapbooks.
Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Memorandums; Photographs; Publications (document genre); Scrapbooks; Videocassettes; Television -- Production and direction; GRETA (Organization: Texas); KUHT Film Productions; KUHT-TV (Television station: Houston, Tex.); Public Broadcasting Service (U.S.); University of Houston
- Discrepancy Files, 1990-1998
  Scope and Contents
  The FCC requires broadcasters to produce a daily program log on all their broadcasts. If they were to find any variations to the broadcast schedule, they are to produce a document called the Discrepancy Report. The original log is updated with that information to produce an 'As-Run Log.' The FCC no longer requires broadcasters to maintain a hard copy of the 'As-Run Log,' as long as they have an electronic version.
  - March 1990 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - August 1990 (Box 316, Folder 2-5)
  - September 1990 (Box 316, Folder 6-9)
  - October 1990 (Box 316, Folder 10-14)
  - November 1990 (Box 317, Folder 1-4)
  - December 1990 (Box 317, Folder 5-8)
  - January 1991 (Box 317, Folder 9-13)
  - February 1991 (Box 318, Folder 1-4)
  - March 1991 (Box 318, Folder 5-8)
  - April 1991 (Box 318, Folder 9-12)
  - May 1991 (Box 319, Folder 1-4)
  - June 1991 (Box 319, Folder 5-8)
  - July 1991 (Box 319, Folder 9-12)
  - August 1991 (Box 320, Folder 1-4)
  - September 1991 (Box 320, Folder 5-8)
  - October 1991 (Box 320, Folder 9-11)
  - October 1991 (Box 321, Folder 1-2)
  - November 1991 (Box 321, Folder 3-6)
  - December 1991 (Box 321, Folder 7-12)
  - January 1992 (Box 322, Folder 1-6)
  - February 1992 (Box 322, Folder 7-9)
  - February 1992 (Box 323, Folder 1-2)
  - March 1992 (Box 323, Folder 3-8)
  - April 1992 (Box 323, Folder 9)
  - April 1992 (Box 324, Folder 1-5)
  - May 1992 (Box 324, Folder 6-9)
  - May 1992 (Box 325, Folder 1-2)
  - June 1992 (Box 325, Folder 3-8)
  - July 1992 (Box 325, Folder 9)
  - July 1992 (Box 326, Folder 1-5)
  - August 1992 (Box 326, Folder 6-11)
  - September 1992 (Box 327, Folder 1-6)
  - October 1992 (Box 327, Folder 7-9)
  - October 1992 (Box 328, Folder 1-4)
  - November 1992 (Box 328, Folder 5-9)
  - November 1992 (Box 329, Folder 1-2)
  - December 1992 (Box 329, Folder 3-9)
  - January 1993 (Box 329, Folder 10)
  - January 1993 (Box 330, Folder 1-7)
  - February 1993 (Box 330, Folder 8-9)
  - February 1993 (Box 331, Folder 1-4)
  - March 1993 (Box 331, Folder 5-9)
  - March 1993 (Box 332, Folder 1-2)
  - April 1993 (Box 332, Folder 3-9)
  - May 1993 (Box 333, Folder 1-6)
  - June 1993 (Box 333, Folder 7-8)
  - June 1993 (Box 334, Folder 1-4)
  - July 1993 (Box 334, Folder 5-8)
  - July 1993 (Box 335, Folder 1-3)
  - August 1993 (Box 335, Folder 4-8)
  - August 1993 (Box 336, Folder 1-2)
  - September 1993 (Box 336, Folder 3-9)
  - October 1993 (Box 337, Folder 1-8)
  - November 1993 (Box 337, Folder 9-10)
  - November 1993 (Box 338, Folder 1-4)
  - December 1993 (Box 338, Folder 5-9)
  - December 1993 (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - January 1994 (Box 339, Folder 2-9)
  - February 1994 (Box 340, Folder 1-7)
  - March 1994 (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - March 1994 (Box 341, Folder 1-6)
  - April 1994 (Box 341, Folder 7-8)
  - April 1994 (Box 342, Folder 1-6)
  - May 1994 (Box 342, Folder 7-8)
  - May 1994 (Box 343, Folder 1-6)
  - June 1994 (Box 343, Folder 7-8)
  - June 1994 (Box 344, Folder 1-8)
  - July 1994 (Box 345, Folder 1-10)
  - August 1994 (Box 346, Folder 1-9)
  - August 1994 (Box 347, Folder 1-2)
  - September 1994 (Box 347, Folder 3-10)
  - September 1994 (Box 348, Folder 1-2)
  - October 1994 (Box 348, Folder 3-9)
  - October 1994 (Box 349, Folder 1-4)
  - November 1994 (Box 349, Folder 5-9)
  - November 1994 (Box 350, Folder 1-5)
  - December 1994 (Box 350, Folder 6-9)
  - December 1994 (Box 351, Folder 1-7)
  - January 1995 (Box 351, Folder 8-9)
  - January 1995 (Box 352, Folder 1-10)
  - February 1995 (Box 353, Folder 1-8)
  - February 1995 (Box 354, Folder 1-2)
  - March 1995 (Box 354, Folder 3-9)
  - March 1995 (Box 355, Folder 1-3)
  - April 1995 (Box 355, Folder 4-8)
  - April 1995 (Box 356, Folder 1-6)
  - May 1995 (Box 356, Folder 7-8)
  - May 1995 (Box 357, Folder 1-8)
  - June 1995 (Box 358, Folder 1-8)
  - June 1995 (Box 359, Folder 1-2)
  - July 1995 (Box 359, Folder 3-4)
  - August 1995 (Box 359, Folder 5-8)
  - September 1995 (Box 360, Folder 1-7)
  - September 1995 (Box 361, Folder 1-3)
  - October 1995 (Box 361, Folder 4-8)
  - October 1995 (Box 362, Folder 1-6)
  - November 1995 (Box 362, Folder 7-8)
  - November 1995 (Box 363, Folder 1-8)
  - November 1995 (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - December 1995 (Box 364, Folder 2-8)
  - December 1995 (Box 365, Folder 1-3)
  - January 1996 (Box 365, Folder 4-7)
  - January 1996 (Box 366, Folder 1-7)
  - February 1996 (Box 367, Folder 1-8)
  - February 1996 (Box 368, Folder 1-3)
  - March 1996 (Box 368, Folder 4-9)
  - March 1996 (Box 369, Folder 1-5)
  - April 1996 (Box 369, Folder 6-9)
  - April 1996 (Box 370, Folder 1-6)
  - May 1996 (Box 370, Folder 7-8)
  - May 1996 (Box 371, Folder 1-9)
  - June 1996 (Box 372, Folder 1-8)
  - June 1996 (Box 373, Folder 1-7)
  - July 1996 (Box 374, Folder 1-5)
  - August 1996 (Box 374, Folder 6-8)
  - August 1996 (Box 375, Folder 1-8)
  - September 1996 (Box 376, Folder 1-8)
  - September 1996 (Box 377, Folder 1-2)
  - October 1996 (Box 377, Folder 3-9)
  - October 1996 (Box 378, Folder 1-4)
  - November 1996 (Box 378, Folder 5-9)
  - January 1997 (Box 379, Folder 1-8)
  - February 1997 (Box 380, Folder 1-8)
  - February 1997 (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - March 1997 (Box 381, Folder 2-8)
  - March 1997 (Box 382, Folder 1-2)
  - April 1997 (Box 382, Folder 3-8)
  - April 1997 (Box 383, Folder 1-4)
  - May 1997 (Box 383, Folder 5-9)
  - May 1997 (Box 384, Folder 1-6)
  - June 1997 (Box 384, Folder 7-9)
  - June 1997 (Box 385, Folder 1-7)
  - July 1997 (Box 385, Folder 8-9)
  - July 1997 (Box 386, Folder 1-8)
  - August 1997 (Box 387, Folder 1-9)
  - August 1997 (Box 388, Folder 1-2)
  - September 1997 (Box 388, Folder 3-9)
  - September 1997 (Box 389, Folder 1-2)
  - October 1997 (Box 389, Folder 3-8)
  - October 1997 (Box 390, Folder 1-5)
  - November 1997 (Box 390, Folder 6-8)
  - November 1997 (Box 391, Folder 1-7)
  - December 1997 (Box 391, Folder 8)
  - December 1997 (Box 392, Folder 1-9)
  - January 1998 (Box 393, Folder 1-8)
  - January 1998 (Box 394, Folder 1-2)
  - February 1998 (Box 394, Folder 3-8)
  - February 1998 (Box 395, Folder 1-3)
  - March 1998 (Box 395, Folder 4-8)
  - March 1998 (Box 396, Folder 1-3)
  - April 1998 (Box 396, Folder 4-7)
  - April 1998 (Box 397, Folder 1-4)
  - May 1998 (Box 397, Folder 5-8)
  - May 1998 (Box 398, Folder 1-4)
  - June 1998 (Box 398, Folder 5-8)
  - June 1998 (Box 399, Folder 1-2)
  - July 1998 (Box 399, Folder 3)
  - August 1998 (Box 399, Folder 4)
  - September 1998 (Box 399, Folder 5-9)
  - September 1998 (Box 400, Folder 1-4)
  - October 1998 (Box 400, Folder 5-9)
  - October 1998 (Box 401, Folder 1-4)
  - November 1998 (Box 401, Folder 5-9)
  - November 1998 (Box 402, Folder 1-4)
  - December 1998 (Box 402, Folder 5-9)
  - December 1998 (Box 403, Folder 1-5)
- Development and Production Files - Fisher, Jim, 1981-1993
  Jim Fisher worked as volunteer and part-time employee for KUHT during 1983-1991, and worked with Bob Cozens throughout that time. He became full-time in 1991, and assisted in the post-production, and editing of film and video projects. In the late 80s he became the station's Development Producer, the fourth person to hold that position. The job involved producing a number of the station's special projects. A short time later the Development Producer's position was combined with the Promotion group to form the station's first Creative Services Department, also temporarily referred to as Department X. Jim was the first supervisor of the Creative Services Department, and after two years he left that department and became the Senior Producer of Special Projects. Most of Jim's productions now deal with a historical aspect; he is referred to as the "go-to guy" for all things involving KUHT archival holdings. These are Jim Fisher's working production files.
  - Animation, 1981 (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Astros, undated (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Ghost Writer - Greenburg Birthdays at the Bistro, undated (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Children at Children Festival, undated (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Cookbook, undated (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from Jim Fisher, October-November 1997 (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - Development Events, 1991 (Box 404, Folder 7)
  - Baker, Carin, undated (Box 404, Folder 8)
  - Golf Tourney, undated (Box 404, Folder 9)
  - Important Message, undated (Box 404, Folder 10)
  - KUHT Training Tape - Membership, undated (Box 404, Folder 11)
  - McDonnell, Douglas, undated (Box 404, Folder 12)
  - Membership Quiet Drive - Scripts, August 1987 (Box 404, Folder 13)
  - Membership Quiet Drive, August 1990 (Box 404, Folder 14)
  - Membership Quiet Campaign, August 1990 (Box 404, Folder 15)
  - Murder on the Orient Express Membership Quiet Drive, June 1991 (Box 404, Folder 16)
  - Membership Quiet Drive, December 1991 (Box 404, Folder 17)
  - Membership Quiet Drive, June 1992 (Box 404, Folder 18)
  - Membership Quiet Drive, June 1993 (Box 404, Folder 19)
  - Membership Quotes, undated (Box 404, Folder 20)
  - Murder on the Orient Express, undated (Box 404, Folder 21)
  - Peruvian Horse Stories, 1988 (Box 404, Folder 22)
  - Peter, Paul & Mary; Sid Caesar and Imogene, undated (Box 404, Folder 23)
  - Pledge Break, undated (Box 404, Folder 24)
  - Pledge Break Form, undated (Box 404, Folder 25)
  - Polo Ball, undated (Box 404, Folder 26)
  - Program Guide - Awards, 1988 (Box 404, Folder 27)
  - Quilt Festival - Correspondence to Ms. Ann Leifeste, undated (Box 404, Folder 28)
  - Quilt Festival - Dub/Time Requests, 1989 (Box 404, Folder 29)
  - Quilt Festival - Interviews, undated (Box 404, Folder 30)
  - Quilt Festival - Production Facilities Requests, 1989 (Box 404, Folder 31)
  - Quilters - Community Quilt with Hollis Turnbow, undated (Box 404, Folder 32)
  - Quilters - Community Viewer Calls, undated (Box 404, Folder 33)
  - Quilters - Edit Sessions and Forms, undated (Box 404, Folder 34)
  - Quilters - Jim Fisher Correspondence, undated (Box 404, Folder 35)
  - Quilters - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Quilters - Newspaper Copies, undated (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Quilters - Producer's Report, undated (Box 405, Folder 3)
  - Quilters - Scripts, undated (Box 405, Folder 4)
  - Scripts, undated (Box 405, Folder 5)
  - Sesame Street Drawing, undated (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Sesame Street Live, 1989-1991 (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Special Events, 1992 (Box 405, Folder 8)
  - Staff Testimonials, undated (Box 405, Folder 9)
  - TAPS, undated (Box 405, Folder 10)
  - Tennis, 1992 (Box 405, Folder 11)
  - Testimonial, undated (Box 405, Folder 12)
  - The Choice is Yours, undated (Box 405, Folder 13)
  - Think Again, undated (Box 405, Folder 14)
  - TOTE Board, undated (Box 405, Folder 15)
  - Travel Spots, Fall 1986 (Box 405, Folder 16)
  - Travel Spots, 1988-1989 (Box 405, Folder 17)
  - Travel, 1990 (Box 405, Folder 18)
  - TV Worth Shouting About, undated (Box 405, Folder 19)
  - TV Worth Watching, undated (Box 405, Folder 20)
- Development and Production Files - Yeager, Paul, approximately 1983-1992
  Paul Yeager was hired full-time as Producer at KUHT around 1983 or 1984. Before that he worked part-time as a freelancer prior to becoming a UH employee. Paul worked with Bob Cozens in the KUHT Film Department and produced a number of films with a main focus on the arts, one them being 'Journey To the Sky.' Paul left KUHT in September 1992.
  - Bayou Bend, undated (Box 405, Folder 21)
  - Cotton Exchange Building, undated (Box 405, Folder 22)
  - Houston Artists, undated (Box 405, Folder 23)
  - Houston Artists - On-line Edit Scripts, undated (Box 405, Folder 24)
  - Norway to Texas, undated (Box 405, Folder 25-26)
  - Robert Frank Production, undated (Box 405, Folder 27-28)
  - Singing Texas, undated (Box 406, Folder 1-2)
  - The Big Thicket Production, undated (Box 406, Folder 3-5)
  - Writers in Society, undated (Box 406, Folder 6)
  - Art Preview, April 20 (Box 406, Folder 7)
  - Auction Art, 1990 (Box 406, Folder 8)
  - Auction - Donate, undated (Box 406, Folder 9)
  - Broadcast Committee, undated (Box 406, Folder 10)
  - Carmen - Event, undated (Box 406, Folder 11)
  - Carmen Sandiego, undated (Box 406, Folder 12)
  - Children's Day, May (Box 406, Folder 13)
  - Living with AIDS, undated (Box 406, Folder 14-17)
  - Lving with Killer Bees, undated (Box 407, Folder 1-2)
  - Logo Contest, undated (Box 407, Folder 3)
  - Making Peace, undated (Box 407, Folder 4-5)
  - Spotlight Showcase Development Conference Spotlight Showcase 9.91, undated (Box 407, Folder 6)
  - The Making of the Representative Planet Eight, undated (Box 407, Folder 7)
  - The Making of the Representative Planet Eight - Newspaper Art, undated (Box 407, Folder 8)
  - Planet Eight - News Release, undated (Box 407, Folder 9)
  - Planet Eight - Making of the Representative for Planet Eight, undated (Box 407, Folder 10)
  - Planet Eight - Inter Office Memos - Letters, undated (Box 407, Folder 11)
  - Planet Eight - Ads Invoice, undated (Box 407, Folder 12)
- GRETA (Gulf Region Educational Television Affiliates), 1958-1994
  On February 23, 1965, forty school administrators met to discuss the Gulf Region Educational Television Affiliates known as "GRETA." GRETA was an organization designed to offer educational television to various school districts. A board of school administrators governed the organization. Through the cooperation of school administrators, teachers, and Channel 8 personnel, programs were developed into the school curriculum. In his book, Public Television America's First Station, William Hawes noted, "GRETA materials were primarily considered supplementary to classroom instruction, although in some cases they were dominant." By 1977, GRETA broadcast in-school programming to sixty area school districts.
  - General Files
    - Award, undated (Box 407, Folder 13)
    - Bulletins, undated (Box 407, Folder 14)
    - Calendars and Newsletters, 1965-1973 (Box 407, Folder 15)
    - Calendars and Newsletters, 1974-1978 (Box 407, Folder 16)
    - Calendars and Newsletters, 1979-1984 (Box 407, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 407, Folder 18)
    - Franchise Provisions, undated (Box 407, Folder 19)
    - Lesson Plans, undated (Box 407, Folder 20-23)
    - Lesson Plans, undated (Box 408, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Program Evaluations and Guidelines, undated (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Reports, undated (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Symposium Brochure, undated (Box 408, Folder 6)
  - Teacher's Manual for Instructional Television Classes
    - Primary Guide, 1966-1967 (Box 408, Item 7)
    - Elementary Guide, 1966-1967 (Box 408, Item 8)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3, 1968-1969 (Box 408, Item 9)
    - Elementary Guide, Grades 4-6, 1968-1969 (Box 408, Item 10)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3 Supplement, 1975-1976 (Box 408, Item 11)
    - Secondary Guide, Grades 9-12, 1975-1976 (Box 408, Item 12)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3, 1976-1977 (Box 408, Item 13)
    - Elementary Guide, Grades 4-6, 1976-1977 (Box 408, Item 14)
    - Secondary Guide, Grades 9-12, 1976-1977 (Box 408, Item 15)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 16)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3 Supplement, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 17)
    - Elementary Guide, Grades 4-6, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 18)
    - Elementary Guide, Grades 4-6 Supplement, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 19)
    - Intermediate Guide, Grades 6-8, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 20)
    - Intermediate Guide, Grades 6-8 Supplement, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 21)
    - Secondary Guide, Grades 9-12, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 22)
    - Secondary Guide, Grades 9-12 Supplement, 1977-1978 (Box 408, Item 23)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3, 1978-1979 (Box 408, Item 24)
    - Elementary Guide, Grades 4-6, 1978-1979 (Box 408, Item 25)
    - Intermediate Guide, Grades 6-8, 1978-1979 (Box 408, Item 26)
    - Secondary Guide, Grades 9-12, 1978-1979 (Box 408, Item 27)
    - Teacher's Guide Supplement, 1980-1981 (Box 408, Item 28)
    - Index to Instructional Programming, 1981-1982 (Box 408, Item 29)
    - Index to Instructional Programming, 1982-1983 (Box 408, Item 30)
    - Index to Instructional Programming, 1984-1985 (Box 408, Item 31)
    - Primary Guide, Grades K-3, undated (Box 408, Item 32)
    - Intermediate Guide, Grades 4-8, undated (Box 408, Item 33)
- KUHT Production Files
  - Budget/Contracts
    - Authorization for Payment, undated (Box 409, Folder 1-2)
    - Contract Talent OT & PT, FY 91/92 (Box 409, Folder 3-6)
    - Dept. Budget FY 91/92 (Box 409, Folder 7-11)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 409, Folder 12)
    - Overtime Distribution, undated (Box 409, Folder 13)
    - OT, PT & Contract Personnel, undated (Box 409, Folder 14-15)
    - Personnel, 1988-1989 (Box 409, Folder 16)
    - Personnel, 1990-1991 (Box 409, Folder 17)
    - Production Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 410, Folder 1-3)
    - Production Payments, 1987-1988 (Box 410, Folder 4-6)
  - Research Files
    - Unclassified photocopies of pictures and newspaper clippings, 1950s, 1960s (Box 410, Folder 7)
    - Center of Learning, 58-2, 1958 (Box 410, Folder 8)
    - Cold Spring Harbor Logs, 59-1, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 9)
    - Cold Springs Harbor Specialists Houston Ch., 59-1, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 11)
    - New Speciation, 59-1, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 12)
    - Script Speciation #1, What is a Species?, 59-1, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 13)
    - Script Speciation #2, The Formation of a Species, 59-1, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 14)
    - Speciation Complete Script, 59-1, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 15)
    - Scripts Jung Interviews, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 16)
    - Unclassified Jung mini film, details on production, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 17)
    - H.L. Hunt Interview Transcripts, 1962-1965 (Box 410, Folder 18)
    - Unclassified H.L Hunt Documents, 1962-1965 (Box 410, Folder 19-22)
    - Unclassified treatment for H.L. Hunt mini film, 1962-1965 (Box 410, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Erikson #1 and 2, 19 and 20, Film Script, 64-8, 1964 (Box 411, Folder 1)
    - Flemming - Bonnell, 1964 (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - Foundation for Hope, 64-1, 1964 (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Foundation for Hope Scripts, 64-1, 1964 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Deer Park Scripts, 65-5, 1965 (Box 411, Folder 5-6)
    - Judge Elliott, 66-9, 1966 (Box 411, Folder 7)
    - P.B.L. Murder Scripts - Transcriptions etc., 67-11, 1967 (Box 411, Folder 8)
    - Unclassified Dallas Morning News, 1967 (Box 411, Folder 9)
    - Apartment Rentals, 68-19, 1968 (Box 411, Folder 10)
    - Food Buying, 68-17, 1968 (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - Par Pines Golf Script and Shot Order, 68-13, 1968 (Box 411, Folder 12)
    - Allstate DWI Program, 70-12, 1970 (Box 411, Folder 13)
    - Allstate DWI Program, Scripts and Transcripts, 70-12, 1970 (Box 411, Folder 14)
    - NET "Pacifica", 1971-1973 (Box 411, Folder 15)
    - Cut Transcript Murder, 1974 (Box 411, Folder 16)
    - Editor - Shot Sheets Galveston, 1975 (Box 411, Folder 17)
    - Unclassified Houston Post Newspaper "Putting Galveston on Film", 1975 (Box 411, Folder 18)
    - Evans/May, 77-2, 1977 (Box 411, Folder 19)
    - Unclassified a Psychology Creativity Film, 77-2, 1977 (Box 411, Folder 20)
    - Unclassified Jung Interview, 77-2, 1977 (Box 411, Folder 21)
    - Cut Script Robber, undated (Box 411, Folder 22)
    - Transcript Cut Rape, undated (Box 411, Folder 23)
    - Unclassified Letter and Packet Sent to Mr. George Collins, Includes a Political Science Study Guide to American Government, undated (Box 411, Folder 24)
    - Unclassified Narcotics Cops, Original Tapes, undated (Box 411, Folder 25)
    - Unclassified Unknown Documents, undated (Box 411, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Cue Sheets, 1993-1994 (Box 412, Folder 1-3)
    - Cultural 1/2 hour performance, undated (Box 412, Folder 4-5)
    - Cultural 1 hour performance, undated (Box 412, Folder 6-7)
    - Cultural 1 hour or more performance, undated (Box 412, Folder 8)
    - Education Television - News, Proposal, undated (Box 412, Folder 9)
    - Environmental 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 10)
    - Environmental 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 11)
    - Ethnic 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 12)
    - Ethnic 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 13)
    - Fillers, undated (Box 412, Folder 14)
    - History 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 15)
    - History 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 16)
    - Holidays 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 17)
    - Holidays 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 18)
    - KUHT Local Productions, undated (Box 412, Folder 19)
    - Local Program Data Cards, 1990-1991 (Box 412, Folder 20)
    - Memos - Production, 1992-1993 (Box 412, Folder 21)
    - Memos - Production, 1993-1994 (Box 412, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous E-mails, undated (Box 412, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Local Production Program Data Cards, undated (Box 412, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Programs 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Programs 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 26)
    - Nature/Travel 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 27)
    - Nature/Travel 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 28)
    - Notes - Prop-Com, undated (Box 412, Folder 29)
    - Pending - Prop-Com, undated (Box 412, Folder 30)
    - Productions, 1987-1988 (Box 412, Folder 31)
    - Productions, 1992-1993 (Box 412, Folder 32)
    - Program Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 412, Folder 33-34)